seibertron.com 2017-02-07

# Privacy Policy - Transformers

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email via our contact form by clicking here.

At Seibertron.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Seibertron.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Seibertron.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Seibertron.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Seibertron.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to Seibertron.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include, but are not limited to, the following list:

These third-party ad servers, ad networks, or advertisers use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Seibertron.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Seibertron.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Seibertron.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

* * *

## User Account Privacy Policy

This policy explains in detail how Seibertron.com along with its affiliated companies (hereinafter "we", "us", "our", Seibertron.com, "http://www.seibertron.com/energonpub") and phpBB (hereinafter "they", "them", "their", "phpBB software", "www.phpbb.com", "phpBB Group", "phpBB Teams") use any information collected during any session of usage by you (hereinafter "your information").

Your information is collected via two ways. Firstly, browsing Seibertron.com will cause the phpBB software to create a number of cookies, which are small text files that are downloaded on to your computer's web browser temporary files. The first two cookies just contain a user identifier (hereinafter "user-id") and an anonymous session identifier (hereinafter "session-id"), automatically assigned to you by the phpBB software. A third cookie will be created once you have browsed topics within Seibertron.com and is used to store which topics have been read, thereby improving your user experience.

We may also create cookies external to the phpBB software whilst browsing Seibertron.com, though these are outside the scope of this document which is intended to only cover the pages created by the phpBB software. The second way in which we collect your information is by what you submit to us. This can be, and is not limited to: posting as an anonymous user (hereinafter "anonymous posts"), registering on Seibertron.com (hereinafter "your account") and posts submitted by you after registration and whilst logged in (hereinafter "your posts").

Your account will at a bare minimum contain a uniquely identifiable name (hereinafter "your user name"), a personal password used for logging into your account (hereinafter "your password") and a personal, valid e-mail address (hereinafter "your e-mail"). Your information for your account at Seibertron.com is protected by data-protection laws applicable in the country that hosts us. Any information beyond your user name, your password, and your e-mail address required by Seibertron.com during the registration process is either mandatory or optional, at the discretion of Seibertron.com. In all cases, you have the option of what information in your account is publicly displayed. Furthermore, within your account, you have the option to opt-in or opt-out of automatically generated e-mails from the phpBB software.

Your password is ciphered (a one-way hash) so that it is secure. However, it is recommended that you do not reuse the same password across a number of different websites. Your password is the means of accessing your account at Seibertron.com, so please guard it carefully and under no circumstance will anyone affiliated with Seibertron.com, phpBB or another 3rd party, legitimately ask you for your password. Should you forget your password for your account, you can use the "I forgot my password" feature provided by the phpBB software. This process will ask you to submit your user name and your e-mail, then the phpBB software will generate a new password to reclaim your account.

**If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email via ourcontact form by clicking here.**
